<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView5"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_weight="1"
        android:text="In one of the barns there was the sound of a winnowing machine, the door was open, and clouds of&#xA;dust were coming from it. In the doorway was standing Alehin himself, a man of forty, tall and&#xA;stout, with long hair, more like a professor or an artist than a landowner. He had on a white shirt&#xA;that badly needed washing, a rope for a belt, drawers instead of trousers, and his boots, too, were&#xA;2&#xA;plastered up with mud and straw. His eyes and nose were black with dust. He recognized Ivan&#xA;Ivanovitch and Burkin, and was apparently much delighted to see them.&#xA;&quot;Go into the house, gentlemen,&quot; he said, smiling; &quot;I&apos;ll come directly, this minute.&quot;&#xA;It was a big two-storeyed house. Alehin lived in the lower storey, with arched ceilings and little&#xA;windows, where the bailiffs had once lived; here everything was plain, and there was a smell of rye&#xA;bread, cheap vodka, and harness. He went upstairs into the best rooms only on rare occasions, when&#xA;visitors came. Ivan Ivanovitch and Burkin were met in the house by a maid-servant, a young woman&#xA;so beautiful that they both stood still and looked at one another.&#xA;&quot;You can&apos;t imagine how delighted I am to see you, my friends,&quot; said Alehin, going into the hall with&#xA;them. &quot;It is a surprise! Pelagea,&quot; he said, addressing the girl, &quot;give our visitors something to change&#xA;into. And, by the way, I will change too. Only I must first go and wash, for I almost think I have not&#xA;washed since spring. Wouldn&apos;t you like to come into the bath-house? and meanwhile they will get&#xA;things ready here.&quot;&#xA;Beautiful Pelagea, looking so refined and soft, brought them towels and soap, and Alehin went to&#xA;the bath-house with his guests.&#xA;&quot;It&apos;s a long time since I had a wash,&quot; he said, undressing. &quot;I have got a nice bath-house, as you see --&#xA;my father built it -- but I somehow never have time to wash.&quot;&#xA;He sat down on the steps and soaped his long hair and his neck, and the water round him turned&#xA;brown.&#xA;&quot;Yes, I must say,&quot; said Ivan Ivanovitch meaningly, looking at his head." />
</LinearLayout>